<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PI-GPS</string>
    <string name="Login">Login</string>
    <string name="Logo">ContinuousCare</string>
    <string name="endpoint">http://mednat.ieeta.pt:8342/%1$s</string>
    <string name="gps_endpoint">http://mednat.ieeta.pt:8343/gps/%1$s</string>

    <string name="permission_rationale">Please grant location permission to start the service</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_explanation">You have not granted location permission. So the service cannot be started.</string>
    <string name="settings">settings</string>
    <string name="title_alert_no_intenet">No internet</string>
    <string name="msg_alert_no_internet">Please make sure that you have active internet connection.</string>
    <string name="no_google_playservice_available">No Google Playservice found. Please install it.</string>
    <string name="msg_location_service_not_started">Location Tracking Not Started</string>
    <string name="msg_location_service_started">Location Tracking Started</string>
    <string name="btn_label_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="description1">
        Welcome to Continuous Care! The app is designed to help you configure your health-tracking devices and allow you to have all of the platform\'s functionalities unlocked.\n\n
        We currently support both the Fitbit Charge 3, a fitness armband, and the Foobot, a stationary air quality indicator. So make sure you have at least one of these available before you proceed with the configuration!\n\n
        We would like to inform you that this application not only serves as a short user manual, but also as a location tracker. It is through this that we are able to analyse the air quality of the places you visit distant from the Foobot devices. As you will see, we have freely available tools for you to keep track of the data we store and process and to enjoy our health-monitoring features through them! So it is important to advise you to keep this app installed after the configurations for full access to our features and assure you that all personal information will be kept private at all times.\n\n
        Friendly Note: The devices we support were thoroughly tested and are certified products.\n\n\n
        Quick Guide:\n
        To make sure that the devices are properly linked and avoid having to update configuration in the future, we provide you this quick step-by-step guide.\n
    </string>
    <string name="description2">
        Fitbit Configuration:\n
Step 1:\n
Download the Fitbit mobile app and create an account in their platform.\n
Step 2:\n
Register your Fitbit Charge 3 in the app.\n
Step 3:\n
Visit the developers website of Fitbit to gain access to the information produced by your armband.\n
Step 4:\n
Once in the website, if not logged in, log in to your account and select the option \"Register an App\" inside the Manage tab.\n
Step 5:\n
Create a new app registration. The content of the input fields is not very much relevant, so don\'t be afraid. You only need to give a name you find appropriate to the application, fill the organization information with our data (from Continuous Care) and be sure to select the \"Client\" application type, put a valid site in the \"Callback URL\" and select the option \"Read-Only\".\n
Step 6:\n
Almost there! Now navigate to the tab \"Manage My Apps\" and select your newly created application. Scroll down until you find the \"OAuth 2.0 tutorial page\" link, click on it and follow the tutorial carefully. In the end you should be left with an access token and a refresh token, save these to associate the device with your ContinuousCare account. If you loose the tokens don\'t worry, you can repeat step 6 and receive new tokens.\n
    </string>

    <string name="description4">
        Foobot Configuration:\n
Step 1:\n
Download the Foobot mobile app and create an account in their platform.\n
Step 2:\n
Register your home device by following the walkthrough provided by the application.\n
Step 3:\n
Visit Foobot\'s Developer Area website, sign in with your account and simply click in \"Request an API key\". An access token will be given to you. Save this as well to associate the device with your ContinuousCare account. This token is always acessible through the Foobot\'s website.\n
        Step 4:\n
On the Developers website, while logged in, scroll down until the \"Identity API\" and click in the \"/v2/owner/{userName}/device/\" button. A form will appear where you only need to fill the userName with the email you used to create the Foobot account.
        After clicking in the \"Try it out!\" button, in the section \"Response Body\" a uuid will present itself. Save this to associate the device with your ContinuousCare account. This uuid is always acessible through the Foobot\'s website.\n
    </string>

    <string name="description5">
        All done! You may now sign in to your account at our website and add your home device and bracelet.
    </string>
</resources>
