<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PI-GPS</string>
    <string name="Login">Login</string>
    <string name="Logo">ContinuousCare</string>
    <string name="endpoint">http://mednat.ieeta.pt:8342/%1$s</string>
    <string name="gps_endpoint">http://mednat.ieeta.pt:8343/gps/%1$s</string>

    <string name="permission_rationale">Please grant location permission to start the service</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_explanation">You have not granted location permission. So the service cannot be started.</string>
    <string name="settings">settings</string>
    <string name="title_alert_no_intenet">No internet</string>
    <string name="msg_alert_no_internet">Please make sure that you have active internet connection.</string>
    <string name="no_google_playservice_available">No Google Playservice found. Please install it.</string>
    <string name="msg_location_service_not_started">Location Tracking Not Started</string>
    <string name="msg_location_service_started">Location Tracking Started</string>
    <string name="btn_label_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="description1">
        Welcome to Continuous Care. This application was designed to help you configure the necessary devices to allow you to have all the funcionalities
        of the platform unlocked. The devices we support and will help you to configure are the Fitbit Charge 3, a fitness armband and the Foobot, a stationary
        air quality indicator. Lastly, this application also serves to provide your location to our system, this information will be kept private and will only
        serve to calculate the environment conditions from where you are.\n
        The devices we use and ask you to configure were thoroughly tested and are legitimate products.
    </string>
    <string name="description2">
        Fitbit Charge 3 was our choice in relation to the personal device that will inform you in real time about your heart rate, your sleep quality, the calories
        you burnt during the day, the steps you done and a lot more important information, but also will help the system to collect that exact data and
        aggreagate and analyze it in our platform. Once again we guarantee that all this information will remain private.\n
        To assure you that all is correctly configures in relation to this device we will provide you a simple and quick guide of all the steps necessary
        to fully connect the Fitbit Charge 3 to our platform and for you to enjoy every funcionality of it.\n
        First download Fitbit app and create an account in their platform and register your Charge3.
    </string>

    <string name="description3">
        Next you will need to visit the developers site of Fitbit to help us gain access to the information produced by your Charge 3. Once in the site,
        if not logged in, log in the site with your already existing account and select the option \"Register an App\" inside the Manage tab and register an App, the content of the fields is not extremely important, so don\'t be afraid,
        you only need to give a name to the application you seem appropriate, filling the organization information with Continuous Care information. Be sure to
        select the \"Client\" application, put a valid site int the \"Callback URL\" and select the option \"Read-Only\", then Register.\n
        Almost there, now please navigate to the tab \"Manage My Apps\" and select your newly created application. Scroll down until you find the \"OAuth 2.0 tutorial page\"
        link, click on it and follow the tutorial carefully. In the end you should be left with an access token and a refresh token, save this tokens since this
        information is what you need to provide when creating a Charge 3 device in our platform. But if you loose the tokens don\'t worry, you can repeat the process of
        following the tutorial page and receive new tokens.
    </string>

    <string name="description4">
        Foobot is a stationary air quality sensor, this device in parallel with external data sources managed by us will enable us to provide to you at
        all the times the type and quality of air you are living in.\n
        To configure this device is much simpler that the last one, so don\'t worry, you are almost there.\n
        First you will need to download the Foobot application, register in their platform and register your device by following the walkthrough provided
        by the Foobot mobile application.
    </string>

    <string name="description5">
        Lastly you just need to visit the next site, a developer area of Foobot, and you just need to click in \"Request an API key\", logging in with
        your already existing account, the site will present you with an access token, and that token is what i asked when creating a Foobot device in
        our platform. This token is always acessible through this site and repeating the process.
    </string>
</resources>
